This is Trigun.
Oh, my God.
We really do appreciate
you lending us a bus bear.
Hmm?
What are you talking about?
If we don't come with
you, we can't do our job!
I'll hate you!
I'll haunt you and your children
and your children's children, too!
Oh yeah, I knew it was a mistake,
but I couldn't take the whining.
I appreciate it!
Okay, okay, you can shower me with
all the appreciation you want.
Just make sure you pay
me back when we hit town.
My wallet's almost empty.
You've got a point there.
Am I really getting through to this girl?
I'm a little bit thirsty.
Do you think that I can
have some of your water?
I'm not getting through to her at all.
Will you keep it down?
Haven't you noticed that
everyone here is exhausted
from the terrible ordeal
in the sand steamer?
Don't worry, I've shut him up for you.
He won't be causing any more trouble.
I really don't think you had to hit me
That is one heck of a
well-prepared dead guy
Hey you
Ha! Ahem.
Well, praise the Lord.
Hello!
Are you all right?
Here, have some water.
Oh, thank you.
Ah, I'm alive again!
I'm much obliged. You're welcome.
But that was my...
What were you doing out in
the middle of the desert?
Well,
my bike decided to break down on me about
100 aisles or so down the road from here,
so I thought I'd just hoof it.
Are you saying you
actually walked 100 aisles?
That's right.
It was pretty horrible.
Gee, it must have been awfully tiring to
walk carrying that huge thing on your back.
I couldn't leave it behind.
I do have my pride as a tradesman.
A tradesman?
I'm a man of the cloth. You?
Are you serious?
Do you like make pretty dresses? Hardly.
I'm a priest saving the lambs
who have strayed off their path.
A soldier of love!
You girls are the ones who
spotted me, aren't you?
You saved my life. Well, actually,
the one that spotted you
when you were nothing but a
tiny little speck on the
horizon was that pathetic guy.
Oh. Hey!
I'm alive because of what you did!
How could I ever thank you?
I am known as Valentines
Alcalinella Zijak Shushirabo Heretz.
Gumbi Gobella, Blue Stradivari, Talent
Trent Pierre, Andre Chartenhamos,
Yvato Vinci Baldos George,
Deutzel Kaiser III.
Don't hesitate to call.
What are you talking about, Mr.
Bash the Stampede?
I hate it when you call
me by my full name!
The Vash?
You mean to say he's
THE Vash the Stampede?
Can this man really be him?
He's absolutely nothing
at all like I envisioned.
How's that possible?
Yeah, I know I have
trouble believing it too.
You mean...
Oh, hey, gee, sorry about that.
I'm Wolfwood, at your service.
Life sure can be funny sometimes.
Imagine running into the legendary
alcohol in a place like this.
Don't broadcast it to
the whole world, okay?
If I shot you dead right now and
collected the 60 billion double dollars,
I'd have a really fun journey, wouldn't I?
I weren't listening, were you?
Got any more water?
I would, but you drank it all.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Hey, they seem to be
getting along really well.
The birds of the feather
have flocked together.
That was a long trip.
I gotta go sleep.
I gotta stretch.
Look, mister, do me a favor.
Please count it one more time.
Okay, ready?
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Recount it all you want.
It's still not enough.
Like I told you, the fare is
one hundred double dollars.
If I give you any more,
I'll die of starvation.
Come on, driver, please, give me a break.
Uh...
All right, I'll tell you what.
I'll let you ride for
eighty double dollars.
Take it or leave it.
Really?
That'd be great! Thanks a lot!
Oh, I almost forgot!
Whoa!
Whoa, what the hell is this?
It's a confessional.
You know, those private rooms they
used to have in the churches back home?
This one is portable.
You must have something to confess
some blasphemous act and indiscretion.
Maybe it's on the house.
Go ahead. Don't be shy
No, thanks Padre.
Huh well now he's not much fun Looks
like you've got a pretty tough job.
Hmm.
Is that thing part of your gospel?
Of course not.
It's all business
Unfortunately
Our church kind of doubles as an orphanage
we scrape out a living doing what we can
we taken all these kids with no living
family no place to go
guess it was time I left
the church anyway I
decided it was a hopeless
effort unless I made some money for them
are you saying you make money as a priest
well I I wouldn't
exactly put it like that,
but...
Mama, I'm really hungry.
And tired.
We'll be in the city sooner
than you think, girls,
and once we get there, I'll
give you plenty to eat.
Be patient for Mommy, okay?
But Mom...
Don't be that way, honey.
It's only gonna be a little bit longer.
I want food now!
Mama, I'm thirsty!
Please, Mama!
Are you guys hungry?
Uh-huh. I see.
Well, I have these.
They're little, but
they taste pretty good.
Okay.
Well, this is yours.
And this one is yours.
And then this one, uh, is mine.
Sorry it's not much, but you
think it'll be enough for now?
Thank you.
Come on, you two.
Wasn't that nice?
Yeah!
I woke up a crumb!
Well, I'll be.
I'm actually surprised that
you can smile like that.
Huh?
What do you mean?
You had me kind of worried.
I noticed that you always
smile and seem really friendly,
But the way you smiled was so
empty, it hurt to watch you.
You're hurting like crazy on the
inside, yet you grin and bear it.
At least that's this man's opinion anyway.
That's why I have this confessional!
No matter what the
worry, I'll listen to it.
Just put a coin in here.
You're really good at your trade.
I've got to be to make a living.
It's not easy, you know.
Somebody come quick!
Eric is completely crazy!
I guess it was bound to happen.
The sun is getting worse
Hey, Eric, buddy, are you all right?
Hang on, okay?
It was...
Don't talk.
Hey, get the stretcher over here.
He's just falling down.
He doesn't really look that bad
There isn't anyone here,
but the passengers.
Now why are you pointing that thing at me?
Well, it was you, wasn't it?
It was no mortal that did
this. Huh? Come again?
What the hell is that?
That thing is huge.
Well, it's still alive.
What is it?
Hey?
Not bad, girl.
Why doesn't anything nice ever follow you?
I know, it's a real drag, isn't it?
What the hell are those ugly things?
Hunts of lost technology?
Damn!
It's all because I changed my route
to save that stupid cheap priest.
I'm too nice.
I should have charged him full price.
Get down now.
How can they still be operational?
Their expiration date was a long time ago.
This is horrible.
Can you help him?
I may not look it, but I am a priest.
Leave it to me.
I'm sure I have a book on it.
Never mind. I'll do it. Okay, thanks.
Helen?
Has anyone seen my daughter?
Oh, my God, no.
Take care of the wounded man! Oh, dear!
What are you doing?
Don't ask ridiculous questions.
I'm gonna save the child.
With your bare hands?
Oh, shit!
You would have gone anyway, huh?
Of course I would.
I see him, I see him.
There's lots of those big guys.
Hey, I bet those are nothing for the
likes of Vash the Stampede, right?
What's wrong with you?
My stomach kinda hurts.
Aw, come on now, tough guy, get over it.
You're not that fragile, are you?
I got shot by the leader of the
Bad Lads about three days ago.
You got shot by Brilliant Dynamite's Neon.
Now that is impressive.
You do lead an exciting
life, just like they say.
We gotta go.
You listen to people,
and then again you don't.
What's up with that?
A child's life is on the line.
She needs help.
Just look for a second, will ya?
They use that thing on the end to
detect objects which radiate heat.
Hey, listen to me!
I don't have time to just
sit around and chit-chat.
Oh, this is bad.
This is gonna be tough.
I'm in trouble!
Your ID has not been registered.
Therefore, you may not enter this area.
You will now be removed by force.
Get down!
Fire!
That's him, all of it.
Hey, nice support!
And you were a nice decoy.
Oh!
Now that's what's known as a nice cover.
You were the decoy that time.
Huh, guess so.
Nice support.
What is it?
Over there!
She's still alive, and she looks okay.
Praise the Lord!
He's fast.
Unbelievably fast.
That sounded like a single gunshot.
Thanks a lot, Bash.
Well, it looks like we're
just about done, huh? Nuts!
No!
No! No! No! No! No!
What an embarrassing way to go.
What is this place?
We really fell into it now.
We're smack in the middle
of their territory.
What?
This is the inside of an alien ship.
You're telling me we
discovered some kind of
spaceship that crashed
here a long time ago?
I'm curious to know what's inside
the belly of this monster whale.
Now that I know what they're saying, I
feel so pissed off at you all the time!
When you're around, things
always seem to get much worse.
My brain's about to explode into pieces!
It's your fault! Do something!
You fell in all by yourself!
You're the uncle!
What's I got to do with anything?
I think we should take five here.
All this is making me hungry.
There.
Here.
That's funny.
With the children, you seem
to be a bit more generous.
I guess you don't want it.
I am eternally grateful for your
humanity in this most extreme situation.
Okay, that was fun.
So what do you want to do now?
I lost 80 billion double dollars at
poker, but there's a little left.
Well, a real man would
lay it all on the table.
Alright then, let's
find ourselves a casino.
The plant's fully operational.
This is an awfully big casino.
Well, where are the cards?
Right here, huh?
I'll go. You cover me.
Hey, I have to tell you, I've
never fired a gun before.
Besides,
if I go ahead and take this one,
doesn't that mean you're going
in there completely unarmed?
You're really crazy!
Why don't you go then?
I'll wait here.
I'll shoot the gun. Okay.
Shuffle the deck.
It's time for a game!
Just one moment.
What is it?
May you go with the protection
and love of Almighty God!
It's the usual mantra for The big guy?
Does it work?
That's entirely up to you!
Wonderful mantra you got there!
Believers will He'll
be redeemed in the end.
Okey-dokey, then.
Shall we begin?
Go, Jay, let's get in the game!
He's good.
That's precise shooting.
He's no ordinary priest.
I'll get it!
Damn!
Please show your ID number.
Leave me alone already.
Unable to confirm identity.
Conclusion, intrusion.
Would you just get out of my way?
Hey!
Oh, this is bad.
There.
Huh? Hey, Vash?
He's alive.
I don't believe this guy.
You can stop now.
There's no one left to protect.
Good night what
happened back there what
do you mean don't play dumb with me I'm
asking what you did back there it must
have been God it's the only explanation?
How's that?
Oh, no, there's more!
Hello?
Are the two of you down there somewhere?
Can you hear us?
It's us, Millie and Meryl.
We're here to save you.
If you're there, give us a sign.
I think there may be...
A little late, I'd say.
You can get out of the worst
predicaments imaginable,
just like they say, Vash the Stampede.
I'd much rather lead an uneventful
life if it was up to me.
You couldn't if you tried. Huh?
Can I sit here? Huh?
Uh, yeah, go ahead.
Hey, you're really comfortable.
Boy, that guy sure has a lot of nerve.
Actually, he reminds me of someone I know.
Yeah, isn't he horrible?
I think we should tell him off.
Yeah, let's do that.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay.
Let's go, Simon.
Let's go. Let's go.
Oh, grote, let's go.
Let's go.
Ah, what's going on?
Ah.
Oh, I don't know.
My back hurts.
Hahahaha.
Thanks a lot for all the support, Victor.
Vash, it was a fun and interesting trip.
You're leaving now?
I gotta get back to work, you know.
Hey, preacher man!
Hey, thanks a lot.
Damn, that thing's heavy.
That, my friend, is because
it's so full of mercy.
See you later!
Try to stay out of trouble, Vash.
Everyone around you will be
a whole lot healthier for it.
And with any luck, we'll meet again soon.
May you all go with God, my friends.
He was a strange and unusual man. Yeah.
And there went Wolfwood.
Okay, I think I'll go get
something yummy to eat.
Mmm, that sounds good.
But first, I need you to
return the money I lent you.
Alright already, we'll give it back.
It's not like you don't know
where to find us or anything.
The blue sky in the middle of the
sky, the wind is in the future.
the sun is in the future.
But i'll just
leave my eyes.
Just leave my eyes. With my eyes and eyes.
I have no idea.
Thank you.
I think I'd like to do
something nice for somebody.
I think it's good if you smile at
someone and they smile in return.
Voluntary love encourages people
to create a sense of friendliness.
Love that is unconditional
gives us respect as people.
However, it's wrong to force
love to try to keep it alive.
If the strain goes on, eventually
it'll bloom into the flower called lye,
the deceptively thorny
flower that hurts people.